# **AU DUONG TUAN**

Designer, UX Engineer

+84 948 935 300 hi@auduongtuan.com https://auduongtuan.com

## Introduction

I am a designer with good technical background and strong visual design skills who helps close the gap between design and development. Experienced in design systems, user interface design, and front-end development.

I had got my hand in design & code since 2009 when I self-studied them to create Yahoo! 360 blog themes and WordPress websites. Currently, I hold my BFA in design and I am getting my second bachelor's degree in tech.

I'm looking for a product environment to improve my product sense and can interact with end-users. Furthermore, it will be best if I can work in a <u>UX Engineer</u> role.

## **Experience**

### **Aperia Vietnam**

UI/UX DESIGNER, FULL-TIME, APR 2020 - CURRENT

Working as a lead designer in a design system team. My daily tasks are:

- · Create and maintain UI kits in Sketch & Figma.
- Document components (UI specs, behaviors, and storybook) and design patterns.
- · Handoff designs to developers. Sometimes I prototype complex concepts using HTML/CSS/JS and implement the React components.
- Also, making Figma plugins to help improve design workflow is my favorite task to do.

On the other hand, do some internal work such as collaborating with the Branding team to implement and maintain our website (using WordPress and Tailwind CSS) or create some internal tools such as Email Signature Generator, Sketch Cloud files downloader, ...

#### Samsung Vietnam

UI/UX DESIGNER, FULL-TIME, JAN 2020 - APR 2020

Joined in a new Samsung design team in Vietnam to build apps for IOT devices.

## **ECOE Vietnam**

UI/UX DESIGNER, CONTRACT, MAR 2019 - OCT 2019

Joined to a design team building a new estate platform in Vietnam Market.

#### Viivue Web Boutique

WEB DESIGNER, PART-TIME, NOV 2018 - MAR 2019

Worked as a part-time web designer for an agency.

## Yeah1 Network

GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND VIDEO EDITOR, PART-TIME, DEC 2017 - JUL 2018

Worked as a part-time designer and video editor to support marketing materials, landing pages, and videos for Phở Đặc Biệt.

## **Education**

## **University of Science (HCMUS)**

BS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, CLASS OF 2021

## University of Architecture HCMC (UAH)

BFA IN GRAPHIC DESIGN, CLASS OF 2016

## Skills

#### What I do **Design Tools** Product Design Adobe Creative Suite Copywriting Whimsical Design Systems Sketch, Figma, XD Motion Graphic C4D, Blender Front-end Development

## **Keyframe Training**

PHP, WordPress

MOTION GRAPHIC & C4D ANIMATION, CLASS OF 2016

## Luong The Vinh High School For The Gifted

SPECIALIZATION IN PHYSICS, CLASS OF 2013

Teck Stack	Management
HTML & CSS	Jira, Notion
Javascript, Typescript	Invision, Abstract
ReactJS, NextJS	
Git	Language
DUD WordProce	Vietnamese

English (IELTS 7.0)